Guide to the Records of the Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs, Leslie Berlowitz 1970-1980 RG 9.5
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs (Leslie Berlowitz)
1970-1980
RG 9.5
New York University Archives
15.0 linear feet 15 linear feet (15 boxes)
This collection contains correspondence, reports, research materials, and memoranda created by Berlowitz in her position as Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs. Materials pertain to the Commission for Academic Planning, the Archives Advisory Council, presidential speeches, and the Goals Conference.
Berlowitz, Leslie
Arrangement
Folders are arranged topically.
The files are grouped into one series:
Topical
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains correspondence, reports, research materials, and memoranda created by Berlowitz in her position as Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs. Materials pertain to the Commission for Academic Planning, the Archives Advisory Council, presidential speeches, and the Goals Conference.
Biographical Note
Leslie Cohen (Tuttleton) Berlowitz began her career at NYU in 1968 as a graduate assistant and teaching fellow in the English Department at NYU’s University College at University Heights in the Bronx. In 1970, while a graduate student and teaching assistant, she became one of three assistants to the dean of University College. In 1971 Berlowitz also became a lecturer in the English department. With the closing of the Heights campus in 1973, she moved to the Washington Square campus and was Assistant Dean for Administration at Washington Square and University College from 1972 to 1974. From 1974 on, Berlowitz held several administrative positions in goals planning and academic planning and affairs including Assistant Vice President for Academic Affairs 1981-1984, Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs 1984-1988 and Deputy Vice President for Academic Affairs 1988-1991. In addition, she was Director of the Humanities Council from 1979 through 1997. Her last position at NYU was Vice President for Institutional Advancement from 1991 through 1997 when she left the university to become executive officer of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences.
Sources:
University College of Arts and Science Bulletins 1968-1973
Washington Square and University College Bulletins 1973-1978
Administrative Papers of Chancellor/Executive Vice President Sidney Borowitz 1967-1977
Administrative Papers of James McNaughton Hester 1962-1975
Administrative Papers of President John Crittenden Sawhill 1974-1981
Administrative records of President John Brademas 1981-1990
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Please contact the University Archivists with specific questions regarding restrictions.
This collection is in
off-site storage
.
Provenance
This collection was transferred to the University Archives in 1985.
Berlowitz, Leslie; New York University. Office of Academic Affairs.; New York University.; Administrative records.; Correspondence.; New York (State) |z New York.; Universities and colleges |x Administration.
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Goals Statement, 1975- (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Barcode #: 3 1142 042261282
  - Report to the Faculties Background Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226128 2
  - President's Outline Speech to Faculty, GBA and GPA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - President's Outline Speech to Faculty, SOA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - President's Outline Speech to Faculty, FAS, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - School Notes--Sawhill Speech to Dental School, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - School Notes--Sawhill Speech to SEHNAP, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Speech GPA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Speech to faculties--GBA outline, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - President's Report to the Faculties--Drafts, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Report to the Faculties--Dr. Bennett--Working Draft, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - President's Report to Faculties--Version 3, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Bennett's Report--Highlights of the Year, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Message from President--Draft for NYU Report, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Unlabeled envelope, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Report to the Faculty--Dr. Sawhill, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual report--Dr. Bennett, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fall speech to the faculties--final, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - VP comments--Number 2 round speech to faculty, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Speech to the faculties--full text, final, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Speech to the faculties--proposed changes by VPs, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Outline--report to the faculty, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Report to the faculties--additional materials for schools, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - President's spring report to faculties--final for NYU Report, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Report to faculties--final, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - NYU Report--President's report to the faculties, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Report to the faculties--version 1, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Report to the faculties--NYU Report, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Fall speech to faculties--outline--original, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Report to medical faculty--draft #3, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Sawhill--speech to faculties--NYU Report version, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Speech to the faculties--full text, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Sawhill--speech to faculties--dentistry inset, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Sawhill--speech to medical faculty--final, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Sawhill--speech to the faculties--final, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Sawhill--speech to the faculties--shortened version, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Sawhill--speech to the faculties--final, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - JCS Spring speech to faculty--outline #3, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Speech to faculty--NYU Report--draft #3, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Sawhill--speech to medical faculty--final, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Burns, Red SOA--The Alternate Media Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Park, Jackie SOA--The Alternate Media Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Solanky, Deep Chand--A Working Paper on Academic Planning, #3: Techniques, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Lewis, Pamela--What Is the Most Important Thing that NYU Could Do in the Next Decade?, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Frayfsinhes, Jean-Pierre--What Is the Future Role of New and Innovative Education Programs in the University?, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Lever, Cherie--What Is the Most Important Thing That NYU Could Do in the Next Decade?, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Boise, William B.--Graduate Education at NYU: Innovative Teaching and Learning Approaches, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Goren, Arnold--Whom Do We Educate Locally, and What Areas Should Be Developed to Be of Greater Service to This Constituency?, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Livesey, Herbert--Whom Do We Educate Nationally, and What Areas Should Be Developed to Be of Greater Service to This Constituency?, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Konigsberg, Sylvia--The Future Role of Summer School Education at NYU, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Adkins, Douglas L.--Higher Education and the Changing Job Market for Degree Holders, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Brown, Roscoe, Jr.--What Is the Role of NYU in Relation to the Disadvantaged Segment of the Urban Population?, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Rosen, Alex--What Is the Role of NYU in Relation to the Disadvantaged Segment of the Urban Population?, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Goals Papers Summary Sheets, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226129 0
  - Stewart, Joseph--What Is the Role of NYU in Relation to the Disadvantaged Segments of the Urban Population?, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Russell F.--The Mission of the School of Continuing Education, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Guthrie, Sara--NYU's International Constituency, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Hull, Richard--Who Do We Educate Internationally, and How Can This Constituency Be Expanded?, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Putnam, D. Harding--A Workshop on Representative Government at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Plans for the Decade Ahead: A Report to the Faculty and Staff of the University, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Patterson, Evelynne Roberts--The Future Role of Equal Opportunity Within the University, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Nursing--The Future of Nursing at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Manuel, Frank E.--University Goals, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Kristol, Irving--What Is the Most Important Thing NYU Could Do in the Next Decade?, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Griffiths, Daniel E.--Report on Planning for the Future of the NYU School of Education, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fiscal Review Group--Report of the Fiscal Review Group, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Dill, William R.--The Computer at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Ellakian, Anna--Graduate Education at NYU: A Paper for Subcommittee 4, Abridged, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Professor Frank E. Manuel--Paper: The First Two Years of University Life, prepared for the 1974 Goals Conference, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Meyers, Morton--Institutional Planning for NYU: Some Ideas to Improve the Financial Prospects for the University, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Payne, William F.--What Are the Financial Prospects for NYU?, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Burneson, Samuel--Increasing Economics of University Operations, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Goren, Arnold--The Future Relationship of NYU to Other City and State Institutions, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Roth, Sidney--Organization for Research on NYU in the Coming Decade, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bromberg, Dr. Eleazer--Memorandum on the Current State of Computers, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Administrative Management Council: Report to Goals Studies Steering Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Frayfsinhes, Jean-Pierre--Institutional Planning, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - DeGrazia, Alfred--Institutional Planning, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Hook, Sidney--The University's Role in Relationship to Ethical Standards in Society, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Ross, Jerrold--How to Make Use of the City's Resources to Enrich Curriculum, Student and Faculty Life, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Leifer, Rochelle--Environment for Students at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Burdowski, Alan--Environment for Students at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Maggin, Jane--Environment for Faculty and Staff at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Kosak, Alvin--Environment for Faculty at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Hester, James M.--Ethics and Business Education, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Huntington, Fredrich--The Character of the NYU Experience, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Frayfsinhes, Jean-Pierre--The Character of the NYU Experience, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Donohue, Mary V.--The Character of the NYU Experience, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Kosak, Alvin--The Future Role of Science at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Guth, William D.--The Future of the Social Sciences at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Raymo, Robert--The Future Role of the Humanities at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - McKay, Robert B.--The Relationship of the Professional Schools to Arts and Science, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Baumol, William J.--The Pursuit of Excellence: A Ten-Year Program for NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Kerlinger, Fred--A Letter on the Future of NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Dill, William R.--The Mission of the Graduate School of Business Administration and the Combined Schools of Business Within NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - McKay, Robert B.--NYU's School of Law Goals and Aims for the Next Decade, 1973-1983, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - University Goals: ad Hoc Committee on the Faculty Council of NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Clare, Virginia--Suggestions for Goals for the Next Decade, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Deming, W. Edwards--What Is the Most Important Thing NYU Could Do in the Next Decade?, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Frayfsinhes, Jean-Pierre--Academic Planning in the Disciplines, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Farr, Nick--Graduate and Professional Education at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Oliva, L. Jay--How Can We Strengthen Undergraduate Education at NYU?, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Tuttleton, Jane--A Proposal for an NYU Institute for the Humanities, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Smith, Russell F.--The Role of Continuing Education at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Smith, Russell F.--Proposed Changes at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Winder, R. Baily--An Ad Hoc Committee for A&S: Goals for the Arts and Sciences at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Horko, Stanley J.--University Goals for the Next Decade, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Frayfsinhes, Jean-Pierre--How Could NYU Strengthen Its Role in the Areas of Graduate and Professional Education?, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - London, Herbert--The Future of Innovative Programs at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Oppenheim, David--Future Uses of the Communication Media: Advancement of NYU's Educational Services, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Baker, Elmer E., Jr.--More Effective Teaching and Learning at NYU, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Kennedy, Eugene P.--The NYU Libraries: A Look to the Future, 1974-1984, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Op-Ed Piece: Sins of Our Cities--final, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Op-Ed Piece: Sins of Our Cities--draft #1, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Sins of Our Cities--revised draft #1, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Sins of Our Cities--revised draft #2, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Sins of Our Cities--revised draft #3, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Op-Ed Piece: Sins of Our Cities--revised, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Background material--paraeducator information, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Paraeducator speech--final, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Background information for JCS undesignated gift chart, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - JCS undesignated gifts chart, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Background information: R&D speech, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - R&D speech--draft #1, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Research and development policy speech--draft #3, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - President Sawhill's remarks for summer sessions reception, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Testimony on humanities background, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Brademas background, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Testimony on humanities--draft #4, final, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - JCS vocationalism in the university, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Memo to NYU community, speech to faculty--JCS, undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - National Chamber Foundation--draft, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - President's remarks to NEH summer seminar participants' reception, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Op-Ed piece--background, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Op-Ed piece on corporate giving--shortened, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226130 8
  - Phi Delta Kappa speech--background materials, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - President's speeches/remarks on research, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Stern proposal--draft #1, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stern proposal--draft #2, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stern proposal, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Stern proposal--follow-up, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Background--Presidential Scholars Report, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Presidential Scholars Report, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Presidential Scholars Report, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Save Our Cities Op-Ed--background articles, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Liberal arts--draft #5, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Liberal arts speech--draft #3, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Case for liberal arts--revised, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Liberal arts 5--final, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Draft/revision, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Background material--Manhattanville speech, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - LCT Lifelong Learning--draft #1, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Lifelong Learning article for Viewpoint in Change, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Background materials--Maryland Institute Speech, JCS, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Medical alumni speech, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Freshman convocation speech--notes--VP Oliva, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Sawhill speech to general educator conference--LCT notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - General Education Conference--JCS/speech--draft #2, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - JCS speech--Founders' Day, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Founders' Day speech--Dr. Bennett, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Founders' Day speech--LCT notes--meeting with JCS, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Founders' Day speech--JCS, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Harper's reprint--The Unlettered University--JCS, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hospital department heads--President's outline remarks, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - President's remarks--Humanities Council reception, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - JCS speech--Investiture, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Investiture speech--draft #3, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Presidential investiture speech--final copy, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Materials on the liberal arts, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Background--liberal arts, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Outline--liberal arts speech, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Outline--liberal arts speech, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Liberal arts speech--draft #1, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Liberal arts speech--draft #2, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Liberal arts speech--draft #2, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Liberal arts speech--draft #3, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Liberal arts speech--draft #3, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Liberal arts speech--draft #3, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Liberal arts--draft #4, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - JCS--Speech to AALS--background, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - JCS--Commencement remarks, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Sawhill--Commencement remarks--background notes, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Sawhill--GBA Pre-Commencement remarks--background, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Remarks to Chinese delegation--Dr. Bennett--Dr. Oliva, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Background material--JCS speech for GE, undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - GE speech follow-up, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Corporate giving speech--research, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - JCS speech--Management Seminar--preliminary draft, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Background material--undergraduate curriculum, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - JCS speech--EDN Associates--background notes, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - JCS speech--EDN Associates--draft #3, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Meeting #1, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Cancellation of May 10, 1977 Meeting, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Members, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Material Distributed, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Meeting #1, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Meeting, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Meeting--background material, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Meeting--LCT notes, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Newsletter--background, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Newsletter #1, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Commission on Academic Planning--Newsletter #2, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - CAP--Advisory Council on the Gallatin Divison--minutes, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226131 6
  - CAP--Interdisciplinary Committee on Statistics and Mathematical Methods, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CAP--Meeting #1, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CAP--LCT meeting notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CAP--Membership lists/correspondence, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Archives project, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Archives advisory council, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Archives advisory policy statement, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Archives advisory council extra policy statements, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - AAC--Meeting #1, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - AAC--Meeting #2, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - AAC--Meeting #3, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - AAC--Meeting #4, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - AAC--Meeting #5, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - AAC--Meeting #6, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - AAC--Meeting #7, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - AAC--Meeting, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - AAC, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Outakes of draft 1--Report to the faculties, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Outline report to the faculties--draft/working papers, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - President's outline report--Working papers on salaries, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - President's outline report--Working papers on teaching, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Fall speech to the faculties--background materials, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - President's outline report--Working papers on research, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Dean Netzer's report on the faculty, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - President's report to the faculties--version 2, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Report to the faculties--Working papers--draft #4, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - President's annual report--Working papers--background material, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Presidential speeches, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Presidential speeches--JCS, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - JCS speeches, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Speech to the faculty--outline, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Fall speech--Master and background, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Fall speech--IDEAS, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Fall message to the faculty--Individual schools, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - President's fall speech--JCS background materials, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - End-of-year speech--Dr. Bennett--background notes, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - President's report to the faculties--all University, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Fall speech to the faculty--draft #5, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Goals Statement--Original, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226132 4
  - Goals Statement--Draft #1--copy, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #1--working copy, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #2--original, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #2--copy, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #2--working copy, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Steering Committee--Responses to Goals--draft #2, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #3--original/revised, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #3 to steering committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #3 to trustees, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #3--trustee version, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #3--working copy, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)